5 4 3
2 say welcome brothers and sisters to
another Wednesday question and answer
will we open up with the Ten
Commandments that God commanded the
whole world to keep brother James yes
sir and God spake all these words saying
I am the Lord thy God which have brought
thee out of the land of Egypt out of the
house of bondage Thou shalt have no
other gods before me thou shall not make
unto thee any Graven image or any
likeness of anything that is in heaven
above or that is in the earth beneath or
that is in the water under the Earth
thou shallal Not Bow Down thyself to
them nor serve them for I the Lord thy
God am a jealous God visiting the
iniquity of the fathers upon the
children unto the third and fourth
generation of them that hate me and
showing Mercy unto thousands of them
that love me and keep my Commandments
Thou shalt not take the name of the Lord
thy God in vain for the Lord will not
hold him Guiltless that taketh his name
in vain remember the Sabbath day to keep
it holy six days shalt thou labor and do
all thy work but the seventh day is the
Sabbath of the Lord thy God in it thou
shallal not do any work thou nor thy son
nor thy daughter thy man servant nor thy
maid servant nor thy cattle nor thy
stranger that is within thy gates for in
six days the Lord made heaven in Earth
the sea and all that in them is and
rested the seventh day wherefore the
Lord blessed the Sabbath day and
hollowed it honor thy father and thy
mother that thy days may be long upon
the land which the Lord thy God giveth
thee Thou shalt not kill Thou shalt not
commit adultery Thou shalt not steal th
thou sh Thou shalt not bear false
witness against thy neighbor thou shall
not covet thy neighbor's house thou
shallal not covet thy neighbor's wife
nor as man's servant nor as maid servant
nor as Ox nor as ass nor anything that
is thy neighbors I read Exodus 20:
1-17 may the Lord add a blessing to the
reading of his word in Jesus name we
pray amen
amen so here on question and answer you
can ask us a question and we'll answer
it according to the King James Bible and
if we cannot find the answer we will
seek further counsel to bring you an
answer at a later time keep in mind that
all big questions will not be answered
and all long scripture questions will
not be answered for time sake but we may
be able to point you in the direction of
a DVD or CD that you can purchase by
calling the office so please be as
direct as possible with your questions
so we can be as direct as possible with
our answers
out of the King James Bible no other
Bibles will be acknowledged on this
program also keep in mind that this is a
live stream and you may begin to send in
your questions at this time even
questions that pertain to everlasting
life we just asking that you keep your
scriptures to a two scripture
maximum all right let me introduce you
to family that'll be taking part in the
panel this evening brother Jerome Grace
and peace Brother Julie
good evening everybody brother Dre good
evening brother James good evening
everyone sister Deborah good evening
brother Sean good evening and we have
the guest caller with us and I'm brother
Cornell sister Deborah what is our first
question of the
evening yes there are several held over
questions that will be answered first
before getting into tonight's Q&A Lander
says Paul says eating food sacrifice
shall Idols is nothing and 1 Corinthians
8 verse4 is given but James says to
avoid it acts 15 verse 29 is given how
should we understand these two teachings
together all right let's go to First
Corinthians 8 first 1 Corinthians
8 and verse
4 and when you get there
brother go ahead and read it and the
guest caller will take it from there 1
Corinthians
8:4 as concerning therefore the eating
of those things that are offered in
sacrifice unto Idols we know that an
idol is nothing in the world and that
there is none other God but
one okay we uh uh why don't you go now
and read acts 15 and
29 okay acts 15 and
29 and acts 15 and and 29
says that ye abstain from Meats off
offer to Idols from blood and from
things strangled and from fornication
from which if ye keep yourselves ye
shall do well fare ye
well so what's happening is Paul is
saying that look those of us that have
that know the truth we know that uh uh
uh that Idols ain't nothing but then you
have to know that you might know the
truth but somebody else that watching
you might not know the truth now let's
look at First Corinthians the 7th
chapter read verses 9 and
10 1 Corinthians 7 verse 9 and 10 but if
they cannot contain let them marry for
it is better to marry than to burn and
unto the married I command yet not I but
the Lord let not the wife depart from
her husband wait a minute wait a
minute that's that's s n and 10 yes sir
it's eight okay well maybe I should do
uh uh
uh
second maybe that's maybe that's 8 n and
10 let me see what it
says yeah 8 nine and 10 I'm sorry okay
not a problem 1 Corinthians 7:
8-10 I say therefore to the unmarried
and widows it is good for them if they
abide even as I but if they cannot
contain yes sir thought we supposed to
be going to First Corinthians
8 oh okay I'm sorry and then read verse
9 and 10 okay 1 Corinthians 8 verse 9
and 10 89 and 10 but meat commandeth us
not to God for neither if we eat are we
are we the better neither if we eat not
are we the worst but take heed least by
any means this Liberty of yours become a
stumbling block to them that are
weak for If any man see thee which has
knowledge sit at meat in the idols
Temple shall not the conscience of him
which is weak be embroidered to eat
those things which are offered to
Idols now
Paul Paul and the uh uh uh in First
Corinthians is saying the same thing
that said in Acts the 15th chapter the
difference is Paul said we know that
Idol Ain't
Nothing But Here said but you should be
careful not to eat Idol because we've
got people that don't know better and
it's a stumbling block so don't do it
whereas acts just said abstain for it so
both of man don't deal don't eat nothing
to Idols don't deal with Idols one said
act said just flat out don't deal with
it but and Paul he's telling you we know
that Idols ain't nothing but then the
person that's weak in the faith and
don't have no understanding they don't
know that the idols ain't nothing so you
should not uh eat anything the idols
because you will become a stumbling
block toil so both of them are really
saying the same thing abstain from
eating anything from
Idols don't have to say
all right hope that answered your
question as we continue to move on to
our next
one moving on Yer SMI ask can I get some
help on understanding Luke
17 verse 21 most read this and don't
believe that the kingdom is physical
they just quote the kingdom is within
you all right let's go to Luke 17 and
21 most read this and don't believe that
the kingdom is physical they just say
it's within
you all right we go ask the guest caller
to share some light on that question at
then Luke 1721
bro okay Luke 17 and
21 neither shall they say Lo here or Lo
there for behold the kingdom of God is
within you
now let's just read let's just read some
let's go into Romans the 14th chapter
and read verses 16 and
17 okay Romans
14 vers 16 and
17 let not then your good be evil spoken
of oh hold on I'm sorry that
was again that was okay go ahead you're
right for the kingdom of God is not me
eat and drink but righteousness and
peace and joy in the Holy
Ghost what he saying is you know uh the
attributes of the kingdom of God that is
what's in you you know it's it's it's
not in meets and rs it's your behavior
but that don't mean that you don't that
the kingdom of God don't have a physical
uh uh uh presence it's not going to come
read Revelation the 3 chapter and verse
20 3 and
20 Revelation 3 3 and 20 behold I stand
at the door and knock If any man hear my
voice and open the door I will come in
to him and will sub with him and he with
me now that's what is letting you know
you know you get the attributes once you
get all the the uh uh understanding of
the Lord the Lord say he going to come
in he come in into your mind it's do do
your mind to come in he come in by way
of his word so his word is in you and is
directing you to the kingdom of God yes
but the kingdom itself is not in you and
let's go into Colossians 3 and read
verse 16 3 and 16 okay
Colossians
three
um Colossians 3 and 16 says let the word
of Christ dwell in you richly and all
will wisdom teaching and admonishing one
another in Psalms and hymns and
spiritual songs singing with Grace in
your hearts to the
Lord do get back get the same thing let
the Lord be in your mind let his will be
in your mind and when you speak you
speak the word of God which is in your
mind that's what it mean that your your
uh body is the Temple of the Holy Ghost
but that don't mean that the kingdom
physically kingdom is in you now let's
go and look at the kingdom of God let's
go into Revelation the 21st chapter and
we're going to read 1 through 4 then
we're going to skip
down Revelation 21
1-4 and I and I saw a new Heaven and a
new Earth for the first Heaven and the
first Earth were passed away and there
was no more sea and I John saw the holy
city New Jerusalem coming down from God
out of Heaven prepared as a bride
adorned for her husband and I heard a
great voice out of Heaven saying behold
the Tabernacle of God is with men and he
will dwell with them and they shall be
his people and God himself shall be with
them and be their God and God God shall
wipe away all tears from their eyes and
there shall be no more death neither
sorrow nor crying neither shall there be
any more pain for the former things are
p passed
away now see that's the actually coming
of the kingdom of God that's why the
kingdom of God is with man now as New
Jerusalem that's when God come down to
the earth now skip down to verse 10 skip
down and read verse 10 through2 okay
Revelation 21: 10-2 and he carried me
away in the spirit to a great and high
mountain and showed me that great City
the holy Jerusalem descending Out of
Heaven from God having the glory of God
and her light was like unto a stone most
precious even like a jasper stone clear
as Crystal and had a wall great and high
and had 12 gates and at the gates 12
angels and names written thereon which
are the names of the 12 tribes of the
children of
Israel now skip on down and read verse
24 verse 24 and the nations of them
which are saved shall walk in the light
of it and the kings of the earth do
bring their Glory and Honor into
it now how you going to put all that
inside of you that is the physical
Kingdom of the father he's going to come
down and he's going to dwell on this
Earth among us but the only thing he say
among men but we won't be men then
everybody will be Immortals they'll be
God and the Nations which also will be
immortal are going to walk in the light
of that city that is the God's kingdom
that's
coming that's why I said in the Lord's
Prayer thy kingdom come thy will be done
in earth as it is in
heaven okay y the king within you is
when the word of God dwell in you and
you're walking in it but that don't stop
the real the kingdom physical Kingdom
from coming cuz it's going to come and
the father is going to set his kingdom
up on this Earth and he going to be he
going to dwell in New Jerusalem and all
the kings of the
earth going to walk in the light of that
City everybody will be immortal
everybody be holy and everybody will be
God that's all I have to
say all right thank you for that hope
that aned your question as we continue
to move on to our
next moving on to the next one Johnny
Caster asks is sin m
measured not by not by Flesh and Blood
we're not supposed to be getting into
measuring sin because all have sin and
come short of the glory of God and you
have to spend all that time worrying
about your own sin and keeping yourself
in check let's go to Romans the thir
chapter Romans
3 we'll pick it up at verse 10 and then
we go
skip Romans 3 and verse 10
as it is written there is none righteous
know not one not one all have did verse
23 go ahead for all have sinned and come
short of the glory of God for of all
have sin and you went around measuring
sin you wouldn't have time to keep
yourself in check let's go quickly to
Psalms 103 Psalms
103 because we are
to serve sin or to serve righteousness
and everybody got to make the right
choice Psalms 103 and pick it up at that
verse eight and let's see what the Lord
said here he is merciful and gracious go
ahead the Lord is Mo merciful and
gracious slow to anger and plenteous and
mercy uhhuh he will not always chide
neither will he keep his anger
forever agree he ha not dwelt with us
after our sins nor rewarded us according
to our iniquities oh he so God has not
dealt with us after what our sins really
deserve nor rewarded us according to
what our iniquities say that we should
be rewarded so he is merciful and he is
the one that
handles dealing with us when it comes to
our sin he just ask that all of us keep
ourselves
straight and let's go to James the
second chapter last place James
two
okay James two and we going to pick it
up at verse 10 because they want to know
it's sin
measured may God handle that you just
keep yourself in a good place with God
like all of his true servants are trying
to do verse 10 let's see about measuring
sin go ahead for whosoever shall keep
the whole law and yet offend in one
point he is guilty of all oh he is
guilty of all so if you tell a lie and
you know it's a lie and you keep telling
them and the Lord Find You warning in
that hey you goonna get the same
punishment as the thief keep
reading for he that said do not commit
adultery said also do not care
now if thou commit no adultery yet if
thou kill Thou Art become a transgressor
of the law oh lord said if you break one
you break them all so that's right read
that last verse 12 for me brother
because this is the law of Freedom you
are free to serve God if you so choose
go ahead so speak ye and so do as they
that shall be judged by the law of
Liberty let the Lord handle that
judgment and that sin CU all must appear
before the Judgment seat of Christ and
that's all I
got and we hope that that ansed your
question there sister Deborah as we move
to our next one yes and the time is
751 daughter of Judas says if the pastor
only says I baptize you in the name of
the Father the Son and the Holy Spirit
without using the actual names God and
Jesus is that a true
baptism aren't father and son considered
to be titles and not the
names yes indeed consider to be titles
share some light brother
Jerome no the baptism wasn't done
properly um so you know you have to
baptize in the name so he didn't tell us
to quote that verse and say Father Son
and Holy Ghost when you baptized he told
you to baptize in the name and that name
is is Jesus let's go to that uh St John
chapter
5 and read verse
43 St John 5 verse
43 I am come in my father's name and you
receive me not if another shall come in
his own name him you will receive so
Jesus came in his father's name so that
that mean the father's name is Jesus So
when you say baptized in the name of the
Father the father's name is Jesus all
right and then he gave that name to his
son Jesus because it the father gave him
his own name because the father's name
you can't get no name higher than the
father's name and that name is Jesus go
to
Philippians chapter
2 Philippian Philippians chapter 2
yeah read verse 5 and six and then we
going to
skip let this mind be in you which was
also in Christ Jesus who being in the
form of God thought it not robbery to be
equal with God uhhuh skip down and read
verse
9-10 wherefore God also hath highly
exalted him and given him a name which
is above every name that at the name of
Jesus every knee should bow of things in
heaven and things in Earth and things
under the
Earth and so
that yeah did you finish it verse 10 yes
yes okay now let's go to the last place
let's go to uh St John chapter
14 you know because that's the name that
the Holy Ghost is sent is sent in the
name of Jesus okay and St John the 14th
chapter verse 26 will tell you that when
you get
read John you said John 14 verse 26
correct yes yes okay but the comforter
which is the Holy Ghost whom the father
will send in my name he shall teach you
all things and bring all things to your
Rememberance whatsoever I have said unto
you yeah so don't just call out the uh
the uh the verse and use the titles
Father Son and Holy Ghost use the name
when you baptized and that name is Jesus
that's all I got on you're right brother
because in Acts 238 Peter who walked
with Jesus say repent and be baptized in
the name of Jesus amen that's right got
gotta bring that name forward all right
thank you for that brother hope that
answers your question as we move on sis
moving on Jeffrey Meyers asked is there
any Scripture against
Halloween any scriptures against
Halloween brother Julius
julus yes it is yes there are scriptures
the word Halloween is not in the Bible
but the practice is uh the word uh
Halloween come from two words it's
really all hollow's Eve Hollow means
holy and E and and we is the suffix of
Eve
so Halloween is the first of three
Catholic Festival days that I grouped
together and they all deal with the ult
and they all deal with the dead that's
why people dress up now they have
glamorized it and made it uh uh about
horror and wites and and uh costume
parties and people come with all kind of
horror costumes let's look at what the
book says because it is a Catholic
Festival day and is the first of three
days the first day being all hollow's
Eve and they all deal with the Deads the
Catholic dead Martyrs and their Saints
first one is October 31st all Hollow Z
which became Halloween the second day is
All Saints Day which also deal with the
dead and the third day is November the
2nd so you got October 31st November 1st
and November the 2 which is All Souls
day let's go to Exodus the 22nd chapter
Exodus I'm yeah Exodus 22 okay brother
James and people dress up as witches
they dress up as vampires they dress up
as ghosts and Fallen but you're dealing
with familiar
spirits make movies and stuff about it
here we go Exodus 22 Look What the Lord
said about witches Exodus 22 and8 just
one verse go ahead brother thou shalt
not suffer a witch to live so you know
how the Lord feel about witches let
let's go to Leviticus 19 brother
James and we going to read verse 26 and
verse
31 lus 19 verse and 31 26 says ye shall
not eat anything with blood neither
shall ye use enchantment nor observe
times now we got three things here we
got Charmers you got thou you should not
eat anything with the blood which is
vampirism
that's why you look at all the vampire
movies they all the the the vampire is
feasting on blood so vampirism is an
obsession of drinking blood so now we
got Charmers which is uh necr maning and
all those stuff uh and then you have no
Observer of times now you're dealing
with astrology the sun stars and moon
worship which the Lord warned you about
in Deuteronomy the 4th chapter let's go
to Deuteronomy 18th chapter you want to
do ver you want to read verse 31 verse
31 at uh lus 19 and 139 13 31 regard not
them that have familiar spirits neither
seek after wi Wizards to be defiled by
them I am the Lord ye your God Wizards
are male witches they call it uh and
they call the women now they call the
men Wizards and they call the female
wicens which is female
witches okay and that that's what
Halloween deals with that is the
wicked's first of eight Pagan uh
Festival days of the Dead let's go to
Deuteronomy the 18th
chapter Deuteronomy 18 so the Lord says
plenty about it Deuteronomy 18 we're
going to go 9- 11 Deuteronomy 189
through1 when thou art come into the
land which the Lord thy God giveth thee
Thou shalt not learn to do after the
Abominations of those Nations World
blown that go ahead there shall not be
found among you anyone that maketh his
son or his daughter to pass through the
fire or that uses de divination or an
observer of times or an enchanter or
witch or a charmer or consulter with
familiar spirits or Wizard or
Necromancer necromass is dealing with
the dead Wizards we is witchcraft
familiar Spirit you're dealing with
Fallen Angel sister and brothers and
then you have enchanters and you have
Witchcraft and you have astrology people
and the last one I'm not going to go
there I just give you the scripture that
is Galatians 5 and verse 20 the Lord
tell you all these people that practice
these things shall not inherit the
kingdom of God so yes the book speaks
against uh Halloween and all the
festivities that belong to it that's all
I got Cornel
that's right brother Lord say he's not a
god of the dead but of the living yes
and all that deal every last one of
those deal with the dead yes sir all
right brother thank you for that hope
that answered their question as we move
on
sis yes moving on and the time is 8
o'clock Malik Shakir has two questions
uh number one in Matthew
27:52 who are these Saints since they w
from their sleep at that time did they
die twice and number two can you explain
first John 5 verse
8 all right let's go to that Matthew
27:52 who are these people that came out
the grave after Jesus resurrection read
it brother the guest caller we take it
from there Matthew 27 verse 52 and the
graves were open and many bodies of the
Saints which slept
arose now these you know I don't know
why this is so uh uh so surprising
because all through the New Testament uh
Jesus was Raising people from the dead
the apostles ra raised people from the
dead the prophets raised people from the
dead so these people were no different
they all was raised when they but they
all died again Jesus is the only one
that's raised from the dead and still
living and became an immortal amen let's
go to First Timothy 6
chapter read verses 14 through
okay that was first Timothy
6 vers 14- 16 correct
sir that's correct verse 14 that thou
keep this commandment without spot
unrebuked unto the appearing of our Lord
Jesus Christ which in his times he shall
show who is the blessed and only
potentate the king of kings and Lord of
lords who only hath immortality
immortality dwelling in the light which
no man can approach unto whom no man has
seen nor can see to whom be honor and
power Everlasting
amen that let you know Jesus only if IM
morality and dwell in the light that's
the third heaven that's the first light
that God created where no man can go no
man can approach and no man will so he
is the only one that have
immortality that died and rose from the
dead Enoch have immortality but Enoch
does not dwell that light which is the
third heaven he's still on Earth so
those guys they were just like all the
other guys that was raised from the the
dead they all died again but Jesus is
the only one that's died and is still
living that have IM
mortality now let's look at the last one
go to First John uh uh go read it 1 John
5 and8
again first John 5 and8
says and first John 5 and8 says and
there are three that bear witness in
Earth the spirit and the water and the
blood and these three agree in
one okay we're deal with him in the
order that he call they said the spirit
St John
663 St
John 6 and
says 6 and 63 says it is the spirit that
quickeneth the flesh profiteth nothing
the words that I speak unto you they are
spirit and they are
light so that's the first one it is the
the word the word is spirit and life
because the word is what teach you what
God wants you to do that's the first one
that's the word of God is the first one
that's the spirit now let's go into Mark
and6 Mark 6 Mark
16 and 16 says
Mark 16-16 says he that believeth and is
baptized shall be saved but he that
believeth not shall be
damned so the first thing is you have to
hear the word of God then once you hear
the word of God and get some
understanding then you have to get
baptized
that's the second one now the third one
is The Blood let's go to Hebrews the 9th
chapter we're going to read
11-4 and then we're going to
skip Hebrews 9: 11 through
14 but but Christ being come and high
priest of good things to come by a
greater and more perfect Tabernacle not
made with hands that is to say not of
this bill building neither by the blood
of goats and calves but by his own blood
he entered in once into the holy Place
having obtained Eternal Redemption for
us for if the blood of bulls and of
goats and the ashes of an hepher
sprinkling the unclean sanctifieth to
the purifying of the flesh how much more
shall the blood of Christ who through
the eternal spirit offered himself
without spot to God Purge your
conscience from dead Works to serve the
Living
God now skip down to verse 17 and read
17 and 18 verse 17 for a testament is a
force after men are dead otherwise it is
of no strength at all while the testator
liveth whereupon neither the first
testament was dedicated without
blood get down and read verse 22
and almost all things are by the law
purged with blood and without shedding
of blood is no
remissions so if ain't no shedding of
Jesus blood there ain't no remission of
sin so the first thing you have to do is
be uh uh born of the spirit how is that
I'm telling about the of the word of God
rather and that is it says word is
spirit then you have to get
baptized then you have to be under the
blood of Jesus so when you get baptized
you are put yourself under the blood of
Jesus so those are the three that agree
in one the spirit which is the
word and the uh uh uh what was the other
one the
water water which is the water baptism
and the blood which is the blood of
Jesus they agree in one you have to have
all of them if you going to get
salvation that's all I have to say
all right thank you for that hope that
ansed your question as we move
on yes Zion asks when Jesus says little
children in many
verses is he literally literally talking
about little children or the
unlearned brother
Jerome it's talking about those that are
believers all the Believers in Christ
Jesus and in his word and he's talking
to them you know uh let's go to
Galatians
3 and read verse
26 Galatians 3 and verse 26 for ye are
all the children of God by faith in
Christ Jesus go to the fourth chapter
and read verse
19 my little children of whom I travail
in birth again unto Christ be formed in
you yeah that's all I
got all right all right brother so thank
you for that let's move on sister moving
on ah o s when the Israelites that are
passed away wake up in Christ's
resurrection and go to the Wild and go
to the Wilderness so again will the isra
isites that are passed away wake up in
Christ's resurrection and go to the
Wilderness brother Julius what you got I
think the question sounds a little bit
confusing Christ is already resurrected
from the dead I want to believe that
you're trying to ask uh where the
Israelite that have passed away
uh wake up at Christ's Second Coming
so I'mma answer it that way right there
because I don't understand the question
how being asked Cornel let's go and see
when the dead in Christ going to wake up
and I mean not just Israelites all those
that died in Christ 1 Thessalonians the
14 14 uh fourth chapter 1 Thessalonians
4 and we're gonna pick this
up at verse 14 because two events got to
happen at Christ return the dead got to
be raised from their sleep the righteous
dead and the righteous living have to be
changed from flesh to Spirit first
Thessalonians 4 and14 go ahead for if we
believe that Jesus died and rose again
even so them also which sleep in Jesus
will God bring with him so when he come
back he G uh go ahead let the book talk
go ahead for this we say unto you by the
word of the Lord that we which are aive
and remain until the coming of the Lord
shall not prevent them which are asleep
so he came the First Time In the Flesh
as a sin offering this time he's coming
back as Lord of Lord and King of Kings
he going to be he's a spirit being with
the power of almighty God go ahead for
the Lord himself shall descend from
heaven with a shout with the voice of
the Archangel w w and with the Trump of
God and the dead in Christ shall rise
first it didn't say Israelite it means
all the dead that died in Christ because
more than just Israel believed so uh the
seven trumpet sounds Christ uh the
heavens roll like and scroll the Lord
come back down to into Earth and look
what he going to do go ahead then we
which are alive and remain shall be
caught up together with them in the
clouds to meet the Lord in the air and
so shall we ever be with the Lord then
those who are Li they got to be changed
you can read that in 1 Corinthians the
15th chapter they must be changed from
Mortal to immortality then we meet the
Lord in the air if we are alive we meet
the Lord in the air the dead in Christ
we all meet the Lord in the air and we
come back to the Mount of ol like acts
the first chapter said where Jesus left
and then we go to Zechariah the 14th
chapter and you can read that on your
own verses 1-4 and it 1-5 it'll show you
that he going to come back to the Mount
of Olas that's all I got on that Cornel
but that's the way I understood that
question okay let me thr I think I I see
what he was away where he was trying to
come well the Israelites that in the
first resurrection Israelites in the
first resurrection some will be there
with Jesus in the wilderness when he
bring all the Flesh and Blood Israelites
back but got some with z zerubabel and
his un which is going to be in the first
resurrection they won't go to the
Wilderness they will be in the land
Building Jesus building the Temple of
God the temple that Jesus going to set
in while Jesus and some of the
Israelites in the first resurrection
will be teaching the other uh uh Flesh
and Blood Israelites in the wilderness
thank you
okay all
right hope that answered your question
there as we continue to move on yes
moving on Ian Wars you to explain
Proverbs 19 verse
29 Dre what you say let's go to the
Proverbs and we gonna read verses 28 and
29 Proverbs 19 28 and
29 go ahead and read it brother and an
ungodly witness scorn scorne judgment
and the mouth of the wicked devoureth
iniquity judgments are prepared for
scorners and stripes for the back of
fools yeah scorning means that they they
got disdain our contempt for judgments
so the ungodly
witness got disdained our contempt for
judgments and the mouth of the wicked
devour
iniquity and judgments are prepared for
scorns and stripes for the back of fools
now back up to verse
25 Smite a scorner and the simple will
beware and reprove one that ha
understanding and he will understand
knowledge oh yeah so there's a reason to
Smite a
scorner because when you see the scorner
get smited the simple is GNA be Weare
they gonna take notice of that and you
reprove a person of understanding and he
will understand and knowledge now let's
go to Luke 12 and we going to read
verses 47 and 48 Luke 12 47 and
48 okay and that and that servant which
knew his Lord's will and prepared not
himself neither did according to his
will shall be beaten with many stripes
but he that know that knew not and did
commit things worthy of Stripes shall be
be beaten with few stripes for unto
whomsoever much is given of him shall
much be sh shall be much required and to
whom men have committed much of him they
will ask the more that is right so that
that is the reason for all of that
there's a reason it's not just that the
Lord is putting stripes on you he's
correcting Us in
measure I hope that helps yes sir thank
you for that brother we have to walk
like we talk yes sir all right hope that
answered your question next one sis next
one so funes says how does our church
decipher what written word to keep as a
standard of living in reference to the
way things were back then some things we
still do and others we don't I just want
Clarity like how a deceased Man's
brother gives the deceased man's wife or
child if he did not while he was alive
and another example and how we don't eat
the blood of an animal because it's the
life of it both are
written right guess
call well the first one first the Lord
is just telling you when you uh eat meat
you make sure that you cook all the
blood out of it you don't eat the blood
of the of the uh uh uh meat that you
eating you have to get rid of it you
know we even have uh uh some of the uh
Italian people they have what they call
a duck blood
soup where they actually make soup out
of the blood of duck you ain't supposed
to do
that instead of if you're going to cook
a steak you don't eat a rare steak you
because the rare is not really cooked
good so you got blood still in it you
have to get rid of the blood that's one
thing that's still stand up and the
other one is when you uh uh brother have
a wife and uh uh he he died and uh uh
you supposed to uh uh marry his wife and
the first child is dedicated to your
brother well there was a custom in
Israel that is not the law that was just
the custom so now what you what we
dealing with now is salvation and I show
you what you have to do to get
salvation and it don't include Customs
let's go to Matthew the 19th Chapter
read verse 16 and
17 Matthew
19 vers 16 and
17 uhhuh
that says 16 and 17 and behold one came
and said unto him good Master what good
things shall I do that I may have
eternal life and he said unto him why
callest thou me good there is none good
but one that is God but if thou will
enter into life keep the
commandments so that's what we concerned
about we're not concerned about a old
custom that didn't work well in when
Israel was a nation that a man had to
marry his brother's
wife if he didn't have a child for the
Lord tell you if you want to get command
if you want to get eternal life get into
God's kingdom keep the Commandments
that's all I have to say all right hope
that answered your question next
question next question Glenn Sirius asks
can you explain Luke 16 verse
9 Luke 16 verse 9 let's go there brother
when you get there read it and the guest
caller will take it from
there Luke 16:9 and I say unto you make
to yourselves Friends of the mammoth and
of of I'm sorry and I say unto you make
to yourselves Friends of the mammoth of
unrighteousness that when ye fail they
may receive you into Everlasting
habitations now Jesus is telling you
here is that look you ain't you this
he's talking about this is an Unfaithful
servant mhm and
uh if you're Unfaithful servant and you
are not going to serve God then you may
as well go ahead and serve uh uh the
world and make friends of the world
because uh if you can't get salvation
then uh uh uh he said gohe on and do
whatever you got to do with friends of
the world because you can't you got to
decide who you going to
serve now we going to skip down and read
Luke 16
and13 no servant can serve two masters
for either he will hate this the one and
love the other or else he will hold on
to the one and despise the other ye
cannot serve God and
Mammon so in other words he telling you
point blank if you ain't gonna serve God
you may as well get on out in the world
and make friends at the world and let
them receive you in this in their sinful
ways because uh you can't serve me and
money
too you can't serve
God and walk in the
ways to it's all that simple so you got
to make it yours if you're going to
serve me you got to do what I say but if
you're going to serve the world you may
as well get on out there and get the
best of it because you going to pay for
it for the rest of you for
eternity that's all he's
saying
wow we hope you choose God all right my
next
question next question time out Houston
says why does the Bible say Israelite
slaves are to be freed after a certain
time and they give Leviticus 25: 39 and
40 but slaves from other nations are
kept forever Leviticus
25:
44-46 all right let's go to Leviticus 25
and
39 okay they want to know about certain
slaves being freed and others
not Leviticus 25 and verse 39 and If thy
brother that dwelleth by thee be wax and
poor and be sold unto thee Thou shalt
not compel him to serve as a bonder
servant next verse but as an hired
servant and as a sourer he shall be with
thee and Shall Serve thee unto the Year
of
Jubilee so all he saying is look if if
you got a brother that uh uh that's
poor and he going to serve you of course
you going to serve you because you going
to pay for him
and you're going to pay him or either if
you he
make a leg with you that he would serve
you he don't want you to treat him like
a slave and beat him and all that stuff
treat
asinger and in the year Jubilee
everybody is set free but now let's get
to the stranger so you have to let him
go you a jilee that's a year
Freedom let's get to the other one ver
verses 44 to 46 says
both thy Bond Man and thy Bond Mage
which Thou shalt have shall be of the
Heathen that are round about you of them
shall ye buy Bond men and bond Maids
moreover of the children of the
strangers that do shouldn among you of
them shall ye buy and of their families
that are with you which they begat in
your land and they shall be your
possessions and ye shall take them as an
inheritance for your children after you
to inherit them for a possession they
shall be your bond men forever but over
your brethren the children of Israel ye
shall not rule one over another with
rigor now that was when there was a
nation but when Israel go back Israel
going to have some
servants but uh and and again too but
you got some people that's going to be
joined to the Lord and they ain't going
to serve nobody
but even the one that serve we're going
to show you what you have to do with
them first let's go in Isaiah 56 chapter
let's look at this stranger this is the
one that's going to turn to the Lord
let's see what's going to happen to him
Isaiah 56 we're going to read verse
three and Skip down and read verses 6
through 8 but let's do verse three first
okay Isaiah 56 verse3 neither let the
son of the stranger that has joined
himself to the Lord speak saying the
Lord hath utterly separated me from his
people neither let the unic say behold I
am a dry
tree down to
six also the sons of the stranger that
join themselves to the Lord to serve him
and to love the name of the Lord to be
his servants everyone that keepeth the
Sabbath from polluting it and taking
hold of my Covenant even them will I
bring to my Holy Mountain and make them
joyful In My House of Prayer their burnt
offerings and their sacrifices shall be
accepted upon my Altar for my house
shall be called an House of Prayer for
all people the Lord God which gather the
outcast of Israel saith yet will I
gather others to him beside those that
are gathered unto
him now these are people that hold on to
the
Lord Okay so
they be nobody slave the bond men or
Bond women from Among The Strangers but
then when the strangers that the Lord
say going go going have to serve us but
then that is not forever because they
going to get an inheritance and you have
to give it to him let's go into Ezekiel
the 47th
chapter and we're going to read verses
22 and
23 Ezekiel 47: 22 and 23
and it shall come to pass that ye shall
divide it by lot for an inheritance unto
you and to the strangers that tojn among
you which shall be got children among
you and they shall be unto you as born
in the country among the children of
Israel they shall have inheritance with
you among the tribes of Israel and it
shall come to pass that in what tribe
The Stranger sourth there shall ye give
him in his his inheritance sayeth the
Lord
God but you see the God is a God of all
people because we have had to serve the
stranger God going to let some of the
strangers serve us but not
for that custom is gone CU after a while
you going to have to give him an
inheritance among you so whatever tribe
that the strangers among when Jesus take
when the Lord take us back during the
Millennium time when Jesus rulle his
very for th000 years after a certain
time probably be after s years or either
the year Jubilee you just don't let him
go you have to give him an inheritance
among
you so that's serving us forever those
days went when Israel was dissolved as a
nation that's all I have to say all
right hope that anwers your question our
next question next question brother
weave said say in Deuteronomy
16:16 it is mentioned Feast of
UNL Pentecost and Tabernacles why isn't
the Eighth Day mentioned if is separated
from the
Tabernacle Jerome what what you got
let's go read it Deuteronomy
16-16 three times in a year shall all
thy males appear before the Lord thy God
in the place which he shall choose in
the Feast of unleavened bread and in the
Feast of Weeks and in the Feast of
Tabernacles and they shall not appear
before the Lord empty okay so the reason
why the eighth day is not mentioned with
these because when you talk when you
talking about Tabernacles Tabernacles is
not eight days is Tabernacles is only
seven days okay so uh the seven days
that you dealing with in tab tacles
that's dealing with flesh and blood okay
the lord gave this man seven days or
7,000 years to exist in these Flesh and
Blood Tabernacles these Flesh and Blood
bodies 7,000 years that's it all right
so that's why you celebrating your
that's one of the reasons why you
celebrating your Tabernacles and they
dwelling these boobs that represent
these frail bodies that's why I tell you
that when you read in 23 so let's go to
that Leviticus
23 and read verse 34 and we going to
skip Leviticus 23 and verse 34 yeah
speak unto the children of Israel saying
the 15th day of the seventh month shall
be the Feast of Tabernacle for
Tabernacles for seven days unto the Lord
skip down to verse 36 just read 36 seven
days ye shall offer an offering made by
fire unto the Lord on the eth day shall
be an holy convocation unto you and ye
shall offer an offering made by fire
unto the Lord it is a solemn assembly
and ye shall do no servile work therein
okay so even though you saw eth day
mentioned in that verse Tabernacles is
dealing with these Flesh and Blood
bodies and that's why you dwelling in
booths according to the verse we going
to read for seven days because it's
representing this flesh blood body you
ain't dwelling in them Boo for eight
days you dwelling in them Boo for eight
days and every time you read seven
throughout these throughout this chapter
dealing with Tabernacles that's talking
about your flesh and blood body that's
why I keep mention is seven seven seven
okay so skip down to verse
39 also in the 15th day of the seventh
month when ye have gathered in the fruit
of the land ye shall keep a feast unto
the Lord seven days and on the first day
shall be a Sabbath and on the Eighth Day
shall be a Sabbath yeah okay seven 77
now skip down to verse 40 and read it to
the 42 and it's going to tell you about
these booths and it's still going to say
seven days because it's representing
this Flesh and Blood body go ahead and
ye shall take take you on the first day
the borrows of goodly trees branches of
palm trees and the balls of thick trees
and Willows of the Brook and ye shall
rejoice before the Lord your God seven
days still saying seven go ahead and ye
shall keep it a feast unto the Lord
seven days in the year it shall be a
statute forever in your Generations ye
shall celebrate it in the seventh month
go ahead ye shall dwell in Booth seven
days all that are Israelites born shall
dwell in booths so and so when them
7,000 years is over bit that the lord
gave his man to exist in these Flesh and
Blood
Tabernacles then the eth day dealing
with when all that's going to be made
Spirit you gonna be Spirit beings right
no more flesh and blood because he gonna
do away with flesh and blood okay All
Flesh and Blood as far as man is
concerned for sure all right and that
happens on the eth day when the father's
kingdom come down and the Lord and Jesus
Christ
present the kingdom to the
father that's all I
got all right thank you for that hope
that answers your question next
question uh next question Lander asks
why were other why were others punished
for David's sins like his child dying 2
Samuel 12: 13 and 14 his wives being
shame 2 Samuel
12:1 and Israel suffering a plague 2
Samuel 24 verse1
15 all right look like three different
scripts but look like they 2 Samuel from
11 to 14 period brother Julius share
some
light
David did some uh horrible things in the
sight of the Lord let's go to that let's
go and read what David did because David
took another man's wife
David Bri used tried to use Bri tried to
bribe The Man David got the man's wife
pregnant and then
David uh had the man murdered to cover
up uh his sin when he was exposed let's
go and just read the the first sentence
in 12 2 Samuel 12 and 1 so the Lord sent
Nathan the prophet to David go ahead and
the Lord sent Nathan unto David that's
good right there uh skip down to verse
seven and go ahead and Nathan said to
David Thou Art the man thus sayeth the
Lord God of Israel I anointed thee King
over Israel and I delivered thee out of
the hand of Saul look what the goodness
of the Lord go ahead and I gave thee Thy
Thy Master's house and thy Master's wife
into thy bosom and gave Thee the house
of Israel and of Judah and if thou and
if that had been too little I would
moreover have given unto thee such and
such things uhhuh wherefore hast thou
despise the Commandment of the Lord to
do evil in his sight thou what
commandment of the Lord thou shall not
covet thou shall do no murder you can't
B people they did a whole lot of things
and you cannot take another man's wife I
gave you everything that you could have
asked for and if they had been little
too little hey I would have gave up I
would have giv you whatever you asked
for but you did things are wrong you
could read the whole chapter on your own
but skip down to verse 10 and go ahead
verse nine verse n wherefore hast thou
despised the Commandment of the Lord to
do evil in his sight thou has killed
euriah the hittite with the sword and
has taken his wife to be thy wife and
has slain him with the sword of the
children of Amma so for that what's
going to happen to you
David now therefore the sword shall
never depart from thine house because
thou despised from your household go
ahead because thou has despised me and
has taken the wife of Uriah hittite to
be thy wife uhhuh thus sayeth the Lord
behold I will raise up evil against thee
out of thine own house and I will take
thy wise before thine ey eyes and give
them unto thy neighbor and he shall lie
with thy wives in the sight of this son
so now verse 12 go ahead for thou didst
it secretly but I will do this thing
before all Israel before the son man pay
back is pay back is something else it
hurts sin hurts go ahead verse 13 skip
down to verse 14 how be it because by
this deed thou has given great a
to the enemies of the Lord to blaspheme
the children also that is born unto thee
shall surely die so now all of this is
because of David Behavior now the second
part of your question is about the
plague the the people that died go to 2
Samuel
24 and David David comforted bash Sheba
his wife uh 2 Samuel 24 And1 I'm sorry
oh I'm sorry 2 Samuel
24 And1 David took sensus but this right
here was not against David but look at
it look how it
starts and again the anger of the Lord
was kindled against Israel and he moved
David against them to say go number
Israel in Judah and so because of that
you can read the whole chapter on your
own 70,000 died because David took a
sensus but the book said the Lord was
angry with Israel
David just happened to be king that's
all I got anybody want to add to
that yeah like to throw something in you
know we are in captivity because of what
our fathers did we are but the lord lord
and we can't get out of it until the
Lord reverse it but it was a custom in
in know in the uh uh in Israel when a
man died his whole family suffered it's
just like the one that aan that stole
that uh uh uh gold or something when
they knocked off uh Jero
Jericho yeah the Lord came in me they
brought him in and Joshua them day they
stoned him his wife and his children and
everything he had the Lord changed just
like it that was a custom but the Lord
changed that and let's show you that he
changed it and you don't suffer for your
fathers let's go into Ezekiel 18th
chapter yes
sir we going read from uh verse one to
4 Ezekiel 18 veres
1-4 y the word of the Lord came unto me
again saying what mean ye that ye use
this proverb concerning the land of
Israel saying the fathers have eaten
sour grapes and the children's teeth are
set on Edge as I live say the that was a
custom what that mean is the the father
and did wrong and the children suffer
the
consequences and that's where it was but
the Lord changed that go ahead as I live
sayeth the Lord God ye shall not have
occasion anymore to use this proverb in
Israel behold All Souls are mine as the
soul of the father
so also the soul of the son is mine the
soul that sinth it shall
die now that is the way it is now if it
was the custom if when a man did wrong
his whole household will destroyed but
the Lord say ain't going to have that no
more he said All Souls of mine the soul
that s it it shall die you know the
children not g read a little more go
ahead but if a man be just and do that
which is lawful and right and have not
eaten upon the mountains neither had
lifted up his eyes to the idols of the
House of Israel neither have defiled the
na his neighbor's wife neither have come
near to A Min Min menstruous woman and
have not oppressed any but have restored
to the Deb or his pledge have spoiled
none by violence ha given his bread to
the hungry and ha covered the naked with
a garment he that had not given forth
upon Usery neither ha taken any increase
that hath withdrawn his hand from in
iniquity hath executed true judgment
between man and man hath walked in my
statutes and have kept my judgments to
deal truly he is just he shall surely
live sayeth the Lord God yes now who the
Lord is let you know that old custom
that you had when when when When the
Children each srow grief the the father
each sorrow grief the children teeth set
on edge in other words when the father
sin the whole family suffer he said that
ain't going to be no more All Souls of
mine the soul that s it it shall die the
father shall not die for the S the
children shall not die anymore for the
sins of the father that's all I have to
say that's in that verse y that's in
that verse 20 that the soul that sinth
it shall die
that's
it all right hope that answered your
question there uh great job panel on
them held over questions sister de we
going into new
territory uh yes the time is
8:41 and uh we are now into tonight's
Q&A for Wednesday October the 23d
2024 Israelite by Blood Brandon
says on the day of atonement I cooked
and prepared dinner but didn't eat until
sunset was this a righteous thing to
do I tell you what first of all when you
speak about Sunset it would have had to
been dark I just because the sun set we
have to say that because some people
think once the sun go down the Sabbath
is over nope it has to be dark out and
then secondly no you shouldn't have been
preparing no no dinner on the on the
Lord's Day atonement preparing for later
you should have just Afflicted your soul
and just stayed in there and did what
thus says the Lord instead of getting
all them free smells of that food but
let's go into um Leviticus
23 okay Leviticus 23 because that was
some work done there that you was doing
this cooking here and the Lord say
you're not supposed to do that Leviticus
23 and let's pick it up at that 27
brother when you get there
Leviticus 23: 27 also on the 10th day of
this seventh month there shall be a day
of atonement it shall be in holy
convocation unto you and ye shall
afflict your souls and offer an offering
made by fire unto the Lord yeah and ye
shall do no work in that same day for it
is a day of atonement to make an
atonement for you before the Lord your
God so you wern't supposed to do any
work that cooking that was work for you
go ahead for whatsoever Soul it be that
shall not be afflicted in that same day
he shall be cut off from among his
people and whatsoever Soul it be that
doeth any work in that same day the same
soul will I destroy from among his
people ye shall do ye shall do no manner
of work it shall be a statue forever
throughout your Generations in all your
dwellings so on that day of atonement no
you shouldn't have been cooking and
preparing no meal for when the atonement
was over so if the Lord be so merciful
and bless us with another atonement next
year hey do better no cooking just sit
down afflict your soul and do what thus
says the Lord that's all I
got all right hope that answered your
question let's keep it
moving yes next question Isaiah 60 verse
8 and N is this referring to some people
traveling by plane or boat to the
Wilderness in the time of
trouble all right guess caller what is
this Isaiah 68 and9 read it when you get
there brother James they want to know is
this regarding people traveling by plane
or boat Isaiah 60 vers 8 and9 who are
these that fly as a cloud and as a doves
to their Windows surely the a shall wait
for me and the ships of Tarsus first to
bring thy sons from afar their silver
and their gold with them unto the name
of the Lord thy God and to the Holy One
of Israel because he hath glorified
thee that's not that sure that's talking
about the time when the Lord take Israel
to the Wilderness but it's also and when
Israel flee to the
Wilderness and when and when the Lord is
back when he bring everybody from from
across the world they all you know uh
we're going to come come back by ships
and by by ples and by ship and by boast
but he going to gather all Israel from
all over the world let's go to Isaiah
the 11th chapter read verse 10 through
12 Isaiah 11 ver
10 through 12 and in that day there
shall be a root of Jesse which shall
stand for an ins sign of the people
people to it shall the gentille seek and
his rest shall be glorious and it shall
come to pass in that day that the Lord
shall set his hand again the second time
to recover the remnant of his people
which shall be left from ayria and from
Egypt and from Pathos and from Kush and
from Elam and from shinar and from HTH
and from the islands of the sea and he
shall set up an ins sign for the Nations
and shall assemble the outcast of Israel
and gather together the dispersed of
Judah from the four corners of the
earth so now some parts of the earth you
have big bodies of water between Israel
and the land so they they going to come
by plane of boats
also that's all I have to say all right
hope that answered your question is we
keep on
moving yes Stephen gas asked Can you
fast and still go to work or are we to
do no work at all while we
fast yeah you can fast and still go to
work but uh there's a requirement behind
that too let's go to Matthew's the 6th
chapter Matthew 6
there and this is even if you're not
going to work but if you say you're
going to do a fast this is what you're
required to do Matthew 6 read 16 and 17
from me moreover when you fast be not as
the Hypocrites of a sad countenance for
they disfigure their faces that they may
appear unto men to fast verily I say
unto you they have their reward so lord
said when you fast when you fast he
don't want you to be like the Hypocrites
you looking all sad you're just figuring
your face like you can barely make it
trying to let everybody know how hard it
is on you that you fasting read 17 and
18 but thou when thou fastest anoint
anoint thy head and wash thy face that
thou appear not unto men to fast but
unto thy father which is in secret and
thy father which seeth in secret shall
reward thee openly yeah so you get up
you know wash your face and you know
prepare yourself like you would any
other day so that your fast don't stand
out like you are fasting and Lord saying
do it in secret and hey he will reward
thee openly so yeah you can go to work
and fast too that's all I
got all right hope that ansed your
question sister Deborah time check yes
the time is
8:48 um ran 64 ask during the High
Sabbath am I allowed to cook clean or
buy
items Dre what you say yeah let's go to
uh John 19 and let's
identify what one of the high sabbaths
is this is this is the Feast of uh
unleavened bread this actually came
after the Passover after Jesus became to
sacrifice for our sins verse
30 uh John 19
verse 30 go ahead brother when Jesus
therefore had received the vinegar he
said it is finished and he bowed his
head and gave up the
ghost the Jews the Jews therefore
because it was the preparation that the
body should not remain upon the cross on
the Sabbath day for that Sabbath day was
in High Sabbath besought pilate that
their legs might be broken and that they
might be taken away so that next day
that was coming up was a high side Jesus
died on the Passover the next day after
the Passover is the Feast of unleavened
bread it is the first day of the Feast
of unleavened bread now let's go to
Exodus 12 and take a look at that Exodus
12 and I want you to read verses 15 and
16 Exodus 12: 15- 16 seven days shall ye
eat un leaven bread even the first day
ye shall put away leaven out of your
houses for whosoever eateth leaven bread
from the first day until the seventh day
that Soul shall be cut off from Israel
and in the first day there shall be an
holy convocation and in the seventh day
there shall be an holy convocation to
you no man of work shall be done in them
save that which every man must eat that
only may be done
of you now notice in verse 16 it says no
manner of work shall be done in them
save at which every man must eat so if
you preparing something for that day you
can prepare for that day but you are not
to do any labor nor should you cause
anybody else to work because if you
purchasing something you causing
somebody else to work
so I hope that answers your
question uh brother Dre also uh the High
Sabbath that's another name for the
annual sabbaths correct yes we have
three High sabbaths Jerome read those in
his question in
Deuteronomy uh 16 and 16 you can go back
and reference that right and we have a
total of seven Al together though of
high saath yes
ma'am
yes all right hope that answered your
question our next question boy time
flies when you're having fun yes KC Lee
says I have read in 1 Corinthians 14
verse 34 that women must be silent in
church meetings does this mean the women
are forbidden to
preach
Jerome um well I'm glad that you mention
the word preach because um being in
church and talking to your friends in
church I know you understand they ain't
talking about that but it is talking
about um preaching in the church it is
forbidden for a woman to preach uh in
the church uh because in doing so you
you're sering you're you're sering the
author that God gave for the man which
is to be the head of the O over the
church and to do the preaching in the
church you know that's the authority he
reserved for the man uh let's go to
first uh let's go to the verse that you
quoted though 1 Corinthians
14-34 let your women keep silence in the
churches for it is not permitted unto
them to speak but they are commanded to
be under obedience as also say the law
yeah read read that
352 and if they will learn anything let
them ask their husbands at home for it
is a shame for women to speak in the
church yeah and that is regarding to
that usurping in the church and
preaching in church because the Lord
reserved that for the man okay
um preferably the children of uh Israel
among among Israelites you know uh
um but uh let's go to that 1 Timothy
chapter
2 verse
12 1 Timothy 2 verse2 yeah but I suffer
not a woman to teach nor to usurp
authority over the man but to be in
silence yeah again that's that preaching
in the church that's reserved for the
man okay uh and often times um you hear
people use uh Deborah or they some
people call it
Deborah and Hannah you know um but they
weren't preaching in
churches you know they weren preaching
over congregations people congregate
they weren doing that they they they
spoke the word but they weren't
preaching in churches they weren't
usurping authority over the man in any
churches okay it's not saying a woman
can't deal with the word of God when
opportunity presents itself you meet
somebody in the street and and it
happens to come up and you share that
word that's all good you know just don't
you so Ser the authority over the man in
the church that's reserve for the man
that's all I got especially behind the
pulpit correct brother especially behind
especially behind the pull pit
and especially among all color Lines no
woman is supposed to be in the pool pit
no matter what color what you got
Julius 1 Timothy 3 and
one and then I want to skip to just
verse five that'll be it okay 1
Timothy 3 and one it says this is a true
saying if a man desire the office of a
bishop he Des he desireth a good work so
now this this is the office of a bishop
in the church it's a man verse five look
really look at this verse verse five
look at it for if a man know
not for if a man know not how to rule
his own house how shall he take care of
the Church of God so the men are
supposed to take care of the churches of
God not the women that's
all all right good add on there hope
that answer their question sister
Deborah time is a ticking and I think
we'll get two more questions in go ahead
all all right Dario asks does the first
day of the month start with the new moon
I see on the iog calendar that the new
moon was at 9:51 Jerusalem time on
Wednesday October the 2nd should that be
the first day why is it
Friday yes
caller well that's because the uh New
Moon showed up so late in the evening
but we went to catch the next evening
and started to count because we using
Jerusalem time not American time or no
other time it's Jerusalem and the reason
is is because the Lord when he come back
everybody's got to go up to Jerusalem to
keep peace
let's go quickly in the uh uh Zariah the
14th chapter we're going to read one
verse verse 16 all right can you speak
just a little Lou I guess caller you
fading a little bit he said Zechariah 14
verse
16 and it shall come to pass that
everyone that is left of all Nations
which came against Jerusalem shall even
go up from year to year to worship the
king the Lord of hosts and to keep the
Feast of
Tabernacles okay that's once Jesus is
back but let you know too that the law
is going to go forth from Israel let's
go into Isaiah the 2 chapter start
reading at verse
one Isaiah 2 and one Isaiah 2 and
one Isaiah 2 And1 says the word that
Isaiah the son of Amos saw concerning
Judah and
Jerusalem keep reading and it shall come
to pass in the last days that the
mountain of the Lord's house shall be
established in the top of the mountains
and shall be exalted above the hills and
All Nations shall flow unto
it go ahead and many people shall go and
say Come Ye and let us go up to the
mountain of the Lord to the house of the
god of Jacob and he will teach us his
ways and we will walk in his paths for
out of Zion shall go forth the law and
the word of the Lord from
Jerusalem okay so we do that is because
once the Lord come back we're going have
to use Jerusalem time so we may as well
start using it now because when people
come from all over the world and go up
Jerusalem to keep Tabernacle is going to
be at the Jerusalem
time and uh and the and the uh uh uh New
Moon showed up so late
and we went to the next evening that's
all I have to say all right hope that
answers your question sister de we got
time for one more question for the guest
caller all right uh Shannon Jay ask what
is the process in the camp or church
when a man forces a woman sexually
should that man be placed outside of the
camp if there are medical records and
legal documents to prove it or if the
brother is still online and in class is
that okay as well should both him and
her still give tithes and partake in the
church well the first thing is if a
brother assault a sister and rape her
she should have him arrested and if that
happen then we will have a legal uh uh
record that show that he raped a sister
then we will throw him out we don't want
his TI or nothing else but just to go
with hear say no we can't throw nobody
out now if he was raped have him
arrested bring him up on charges then
what will happen is you can bring those
and show us what He happened then he
will not be in the Israelite God not
function in the Israelite God but unless
you have him arrested and come up with
some legal paper showing that he is
guilty we would be guilty if we moved
against
him that's all I have to
say all right sister de time
check uh the time is nine
o'clock all right we have ran out of
time we want to thank everybody from all
around the world who tuned in with
us we had uh we took joy and partaking
in your answering of your questions as
we answered them and we' like to say
that if you submitted a question and we
have opportunity to get to it please
don't resubmit sister Deborah take your
question put it in rotation and we will
answer that question next week so thank
you again and until we all come together
again be safe out there be blessed and
may Lord have mercy on us all as brother
James closes us
up Our Father which art in heaven
Hallowed be thy name thy kingdom come
thy will be done in earth as it is in
heaven
give us this day our daily bread and
forgive us our debts as we forgive our
debtors and lead us not into temptation
but Deliver Us from Evil for thine is
the kingdom and the power and the glory
forever in Jesus name we pray amen amen
amen good night all